City of Newburgh Urban Renewal; Collection apap375
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Appraisals, 1935-1987; 2; 21 cubic ft.
  - Appraisal of Property Located at 327-329 Water Street, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 4-3-2, 332-340 Water St. Lot 5-8 (NYR 189), 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 4-3-1, 335 Water St., Lot 28 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - 4-3-1, 337 Water St., Lot 27 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - 4-3-1, Lot 26, 339 Water St., Sarah Pollack (NYR 189), 1973-1976; 1978 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Block 4-3-1, Parcel 26, 339 Water Street (NYR 189), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 4-3-1, 341 Water St., Lot 25 (NYR 189), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - 4-3-1, 343-47 Water St., Lot 22-24 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 4-3-2, Water St., Lot 19 Leonard Engine (NYR 189), 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 4-3-2, 348 Water St., Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 4-3-1, 349 Water St., Lot 21 (NYR 189), 1937; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - 4-3-1, 351 Water St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - 4-3-1, 353 Water St., Lot 14A (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - 4-3-1, 355 Water St., Lot 15-16 (NYR 189), 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - 4-3-1, 357-361 Water St., Lot 17 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - 4-3-1, 363 Water St., Lot 18 (NYR 189), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - 4-3-2, 364-366 Water St., Lot 20-21-23 (NYR 189), 1953; 1966; 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 4-3-1, 365 Water St., Lot 19 (NYR 189), 1970; Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - 4-3-1, 367-375 Water St., Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - 4-3-3, 368-370 Water Street, Lot 1-3 (NYR 189), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 4-3-3, 372-374 Water St., Lot 4-5 (NYR 189), 1944; 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 4-3-3, 376-84 Water St., Lot 6-9 (NYR 189), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Allan Kuslansky, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Appraisal Block 2-1-3 Parcel 41 Property of William Elfers, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Appraisal City Library Block 2-5-5 Parcels 8 and 9, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Appraisal- Combat Realty Corp., Block 2-4-4, Parcel 10-11-12, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Appraisal- Copley Trading Company, Inc., 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Appraisal- Copley Trading Company, Inc., Block 3-1-9 Parcel 8-9, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Appraisal- David J. and Lynne B. Walker, Block 2-5-5, Lot 5, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Appraisal East Newburgh Urban Renewal Parcels 28A and 34, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Appraisal East Newburgh Urban Renewal Parcels 6 and 6A, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Appraisal Newburgh Plumbing & Heating Supplies, Block 2-1-3, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Appraisal owned by Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Appraisal Owned by Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Appraisal- Parkhill Harris Block 4-3-2, Lot 36-43, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Appraisal- Property of Clarence and Helen Klein, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Appraisal- Property of Jean Frankel Block 2-5-5 Parcel 24, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Appraisal Property of M. Raymond Rosenblum Inc., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Appraisal Property of Morris and Fanny Levy, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis (NYR 189), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis cont'd for Lake Street, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis East Newburgh Project, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis for Arthur Miller etc., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis for Lake Street, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis NDP NY A-10 Lake St., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis Norman Shapiro, 1971; 1973 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis- Norman Shapiro, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Appraisal Review East Newburgh Project, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Appraisal Review East Newburgh Project District 2 Map 1 Block 2, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Appraisal Reviews and Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Appraisal Reviews for Proclaimer's Certificates, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Appraisal Reviews for Proclaimer's Certificates, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Appraisal Ruth E. Coleman Block 2-1-3, Parcel 17 and 18, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Appraisal- Samuel N. Berkowsky, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Appraisal- Water Street Urban Renewal Project, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Argenio Brothers, Inc., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Armo Contractors, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Arthur Olick Acquisition, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Artko Wrecking Co, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Block 2-1-3, Parcel 45, Property of Quentin Skipwith, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Block 2-1-3, Parcel 48, Property of Quentin Skipwith, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Block 3-1-11, Lot 17-19, Property of Carl Silverstein, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Boice Wheeler, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Clifford and Margaret Smith Block 2-1-2 Parcel 1-3, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Copy to be used at Trial (red lettering), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Cosmie R. and Joseph S Safiotti, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Cost Estimates and Appraisals, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - David Tower, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - DeLeuw, Cather, and Co., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Disposition Parcel Numbers 1, 2, 12, 13, 18, 20-24, 27-28, 30, 32., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - DMB 4-1-3 Lot 2, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - DMB 4-1-3 Lot 7 and 8 Ashton Rowell Property, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Donnaruma Appraisals NYR 189 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - East Newburgh Project R-189, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - East Newburgh R-189 Board of Education Building Parcel 2-5-5, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - East Newburgh Urban Renewal Project Parcels Nos. 8 and 15, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - EC + Thelma Moulton/ Lucille Cole (NYR 189), 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - EC and Thelma Moulton Appraisal, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Edward Weickert, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Fixture & Machinery Appraisal CJ Drislane Co. Inc, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Fixture & Machinery Appraisal Louis Nuzzo Construction Corp., 1970 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Fixture & Machinery Appraisal Newburgh Frame and Axle, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Fixture and Equipment Appraisal Sylcox Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Fixture and Machinery Appraisal Banjo Restaurant, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Fixture and Machinery Appraisal Costa Beverages Larkin Property, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Fixture and Machinery Appraisal Highland Provision Co., 1970 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Fixture and Machinery Appraisal John Barra, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fixture and Machinery Appraisal Kay's Lunch Lake Street, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Fixture and Machinery Appraisal Larkin Ice House Cold Storage, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Fixture and Machinery Appraisal Rocco Handbag Corporation, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Flynn Appraisal, 1969; 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Flynn Contract NYA-10 Appraisers, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Frank S. Pucino, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Henry Temes, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - HR Fountain + Co. Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Industrial Park (NYR 189), 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - J and R Equipment (NYR 189), 1974; 1976 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - James J. Briody, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Jerome Haims Realty Inc., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - John McLean Acquisition, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Jules Pomerantz, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Jules Pomerantz Appraiser Terms, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Julius and Ann Johnson Property, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Kartigaines Acquisition, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Letter of Consent (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Loan and Grant Appl Part 1, NYR 189 (NYR 189), 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Michael Fayo Jr., 1976 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Michael Quinn, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Mid Hudson Backhoe Services Inc., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Milton Chazan Associates, 1975; 1977 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - NAID Demolition (NYR 189), 1966; 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Vermont Terminal Corporation, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Newburgh Plumbing and Heating Supplies, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency NDP NY A-10 Lake Street (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency NDP NYA-10 Lake Street, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - NURA Comparable Sales Data for NYR 189 Volume 1 (NYR 189), 1961-1965; 1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - NURA disposition (NYR 189), 1951; 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - NURA NYR 189 Flynn Appraisals with Photos 1-1-2 Lot 26 to 2-1-3, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - NURA NYR 189 Flynn Appraisals with Photos 1-1-2 Lots 1-33, 1969; Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - NURA NYR 189 Flynn Appraisals with Photos 2-5-5 + 4-5-2 (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NURA NYR-189 Mid-Hudson Backhoe Service (NYR 189), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - NURA Public Safety Building Landfill Contract (NYR 189), 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NURA Spiral Notebook (NYR 189), 1969; Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - NYR 189 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - NYR 189 Meetings Arranged NURA 1968 (NYR 189) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NYR 189 Parcel 3-2-5, Lot 44, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Office Copy Reuse Appraisal Disposition Parcels 2, 3, 10, 10A, 11A, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Plaintiff's Copy Appraisal Samuel N. Berkowsky, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Property of Lucille Cole, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Raymond, Perish, and Pine, Inc., 1969; 1973 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Reuse Appraisal Disposition Parcels 3, 5A, 5b, 9 and 14, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Reuse Appraisal Newburgh City Library Parcel 2-5-5 Lot 9, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Reuse Appraisal NYA-10 Lake Street Urban Renewal Area, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Reuse Appraisal Parcels 3, 5A, 5B, 9, 14, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Reuse Appraisal Parcels No. 6 and 6A, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Reuse Appraisal Water Street between Bourne and Broad, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Richard Venuti, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Right of Way Between 5th Street and South Street (NYR 189), 1968; 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Rusciano Appraisers + Consultants, Inc., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Sales Brochure and Valuation Analysis as of March 26, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Samuel N. Berkowsky, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - SAS Equipment Co., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Second Reuse Appraisal for City of Newburgh (Yellow), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Second Street South Side between Grand and Montgomery, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Second Street South Side between Grand and Montgomery, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Solomon and Mamie Ware Property, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Stephen M. Bull Inc., 1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Thalle Construction Co., 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Traphagen Building, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Tuscan Villa Reuse Appraisal Block 3-2-5 Parcels 45-48, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Updating Lake Street Project, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 11 URA Property Acquisition (NYR 189), 1960; 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 11 URA Working Papers (NYR 189), 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Vincent J. Cestaro & Son, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Weisblatt Electric Company Block 2-1-2 Lot 34, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - William and Calliope Komondorea, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - William J. McIntyre, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Willie L. Owens, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Engineering Department, 1949-1986; 3; 12 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains demolition contracts, engineering plans, maps, and compliance bids.
  - 701 Planning Project, NYP 121 Urban Assist, 1965-1970; 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1976 Urban Renewal Agency Restructuring (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Applications for Variance Map, 1964; 1967 (Box 7, Item 1)
  - Bid Opening Friday, July 19, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bids Rec'd Oct. 20, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Urban Renewal Project Survey and Planning Application, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Building-Housing Code Violations Map, 1967 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - Bus Route Maps (Box 7, Item 3)
    Includes Beacon Return, Stewart Field Return, Orange Lake Return, Southside 1s Return of Crosstown Route, Crosstown Return, Broadway, Cornwall Return, and Northside Return
  - Bus Routes Map Prepared by E.H., 1970 (Box 7, Item 4)
    Includes Broadway, Northside, Crosstown, Orange Line, and Stewart Field
  - Bus Routes Map Prepared by H.G. Hotchner, 1965 (Box 7, Item 5)
    Includes Eastern Greyhound, Mountainview Coach Line, Mohawk Coach Line, Hudson Transit Line, and Newburgh Beacon Line
  - Central Business District (CBD), 1963-1965; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CF Consultants, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - City of Newburgh 5 Year Systemic Inspection Program Map, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - City of Newburgh Code Compliance Areas Map, Code Compliance Statistics and Boundaries, 1968 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - City of Newburgh Damaged Properties Indication Map, Undated (Box 7, Item 7)
  - Claims, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Colden Street North of Broadway to First Street Urban Ren Parcel 5B, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Comm. Dev. Small Cities Program 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Contract Documents Manhole Installation Project Montg. Street, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Contracts #1 and #8, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Contracts Pending Demolition NYM 15G, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Demo Contract #11 Inspection Reports, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Demo Contract No. 1 Adden, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Demolition 331 Water Street, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Demolition 48-50 Smith Street Pending, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Demolition Contr No. 1 Code Compliance, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Demolition Contr No. 1 Code Compliance Bids Opened Sept 16, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Demolition Contract #11 NYR-12, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Demolition Contract #2 Blue, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Demolition Contract #2 Green, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Demolition Contract #7, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Demolition Contract #7 Urban Renewal Department, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Demolition Contract #8, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Demolition Contract Community Dev, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Demolition Contract Number, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Demolition Contracts 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Demolition Federal Grant NY M10, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Demolition Map, 1967 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - Demolition No. 1 Colden St & 3-5 Colden St Pending, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Disposition Plot: East Newburgh Urban Renewal Project, 1977 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - East Newburgh Urban Renewal Project Handmade Map with Disposition Tabulation, Undated (Box 7, Item 11)
  - Fayo, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fayo Corresp., 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Final Project Report, 1965-1967; Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Final Project Report Loan and Grant, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Final Project Report Part 1 of 2, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Final Project Report Part 2 of 2, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Heidenreich Cross Section Montgomery Street, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Herb Kartiganer, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Interstate Indust. UR Project No. I-1, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Johnston, Chamber, Lander Phase 1 Community Development, Drawing 1, Annotated, 1975 (Box 7, Item 12)
  - Johnston, Chamber, Lander Phase 1 Community Development, Drawing 2, 1975 (Box 7, Item 13)
  - Johnston, Chamber, Lander Phase 1 Community Development, Drawing 3, 1975 (Box 7, Item 14)
  - Johnston, Chamber, Lander Phase 1 Community Development, Drawing 3, Annotated, 1975 (Box 7, Item 15)
  - Lake St Drive North St Opening Permit to Install 24" Storm Drain, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Land Use Map of Code Areas, Undated (Box 7, Item 16)
  - Lower Broadway Project Area Map, Undated (Box 7, Item 17)
  - Map of Proposed and Existing Community Facilities (7a), Undated (Box 7, Item 18)
  - Map of Proposed Curbs and Sidewalks (labeled 7c), Undated (Box 7, Item 19)
  - Map of Proposed Street Improvements (labeled 7b), Undated (Box 7, Item 20)
  - Map of Proposed Street Signs and Trees, Undated (Box 7, Item 21)
  - Map of the City of Newburgh New York, Districts, Undated (Box 7, Item 22)
  - Map of the City of Newburgh New York, Highlighted (1 of 3), Undated (Box 7, Item 23)
  - Map of the City of Newburgh New York, Highlighted (2 of 3), Undated (Box 7, Item 24)
  - Map of the City of Newburgh New York, Highlighted (3 of 3), Undated (Box 7, Item 25)
  - Map of the City of Newburgh New York, Highlighted and Numbered, Undated (Box 7, Item 26)
  - Maps of Urban Renewal Areas (Proposed and Existing), Demolition Areas (Proposed and Existing), Proposed Code Enforcement Areas, Undated (Box 7, Item 27)
  - Maps, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Maps and Letters Montgomery, Second and Smith Streets, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Material Charges, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Miron Home Center Access to Lake Street, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Misc Agreements and Correspondence Documents 1 of 2, 1966-1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Misc Agreements and Correspondence Documents 2 of 2, 1962; 1965-1966; 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Misc Estimates, 1961-1963; Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Montgomery Street Rehabilitation, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Montgomery Street William Lewis, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - NDP, NURA, Preliminary by Raymond, May, Parish and Pine Pt 3, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NDP, NURA, Preliminary by Raymond, May, Parish, and Pine Pt 1, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NDP, NURA, Preliminary by Raymond, May, Parish, and Pine Pt 2, 1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - North St., Powell Ave., Liberty St., Central Ave., Carobene Court, Elmwood Place Map, 1965 (Box 7, Item 28)
  - NURA, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NYA 10 Demol Contr #1 Lake Street, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - NYM 15G Demo Contr #1, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NYR 189 Demol Contr #11, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NYR 189 Demol Contr No. 3, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - NYR 189 Demol Contr No. 4, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - NYR 189 Demol Contr No. 5, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - NYR 189 Demol Contr No. 6, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Official Zoning Map, 1955 (Box 7, Item 29)
  - Original and New Urban Renewal Areas (Box 7, Item 30)
  - Personnel Charges and Street Improvements, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Parcel No. 4 Water Street Project Map, 1967 (Box 7, Item 31)
  - Planning for Arterial Routes, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Item 32)
  - Possible Development Sites and 9W Alternate Route, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Item 33)
  - Project NYR 189, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Surface Treatment, 1964 (Box 7, Item 34)
  - Public Impvmts County, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Scott Woodhull Clerk of Works Agreement, Quantity Estimates, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Specifications for Demolition and Site Clearance, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Specifications for Demolition Contract Number 1, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Specifications for Street Improvements U.R. N.Y. 12, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Specifications for Street Improvements U.R. N.Y. 12 (2 of 3), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Specifications for Street Improvements U.R. N.Y. 12 (3 of 3), 1963; Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Street Resurfacing Various, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Street Tarring Program Map, Undated (Box 7, Item 35)
  - Undergrounding of Electric & Tel. Service, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - UR Demolition Contract #10, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - UR Demolition Contract #10, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - UR Demolition Contract #5, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - UR Demolition Contract #6, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - UR Disposition Parcel #32, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - UR Disposition Parcel Location Map, 1986 (Box 7, Item 36)
  - UR Disposition Parcel No. 34 Water St between Broad and Nicoll, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - UR Inspection Reports Demo #7 Federal, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - UR Inspection Reports Demo #7 Ours, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - UR Inspection Reports Demo Contract #8 Federal, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - UR Inspection Reports Demo Contract #8 Ours, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - UR Montgomery Street Rehabilitation 1969, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - UR NYM 10 Demo Contr #2, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - UR Street Improvements Preliminary Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - UR Test Borings, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Urb Ren Demolition Contrs, 1961-1969; Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Urban Development Corp. (UDC), Citizens Advisory Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Urban Development Corp. (UDC), Lake St. Housing Proposal, Miron Lumber Prop., 1954; 1968-1969; 1972; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Urban Development Corp. (UDC), Library and Bd of Education Building, Grand & 2nd Sts "Court House Square" Proj, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Urban Development Corp. (UDC), Neighborhood Devel. Area #3 - "Central North" Bet. Broadway and First; Liberty & Johnston, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Urban Development Corp. (UDC), Office Bldg Prop. For B'Way & Johnston Sts, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Urban Development Corporation Canada Dry Inc. Building Lake St., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Urban Development Plan (Map) with Sections for Federal Code Enforcement Project, HUD Rehab Project, Urban Development Proposal, Urban Renewal, and Containership Port, Undated (Box 7, Item 37)
  - Urban Ren NYR-12 Demol. Contr. #9, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Urban Renewal Areas Map, Undated (Box 7, Item 38)
  - Urban Renewal - Water Street, NYR - 12, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - Water Street, NYR - 12, 1969-1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal Agency, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Urban Renewal Agency, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal Agency, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal Agency Meetings and Minutes, 1969-1970; 1973; Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Annual Reports, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Application for Loan & Grant NYR 189A Part 1, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal Central Hudson, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal Certification Non Cash Grant in Aid, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal Correspondence, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal Correspondence, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Correspondence Acquisitions and Appraisals, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Cost Estimates and Appraisals, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract #1, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract #1 Ours, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract #2, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract #3 Part 1, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract #3 Part 2, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract #3 Part 3, 1962; 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract #4- Unsafe Buildings, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Contract #9, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Dump Sites, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal Demolition Work Sheets Contract #3 Parts 1, 2, 3, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)